soft engine radio episode 127 interview
with your kima hotter on usability
[Music]
this is software engineering radio the
podcast for professional developers on
the web at se - radio dotnet
ester radio brings you relevant and
detailed discussions and interviews on
software engineering topics every 10
days thanks to our audience and the
partners listed on our website for
support
[Music]
okay welcome listeners to another
episode of software engineering radio
this time we are talking about usability
and design issues our guest today is you
have him my heart from UID thank you why
don't you introduce yourself in your
company a little bit so people know who
they're listening to okay fine my name
is Yanni Mahara as you said and I'm
working at user interface design which
is a company dealing offering usability
services a few words about myself
I have studied computer science at
University of Stuttgart sources in
Germany and I've been working at
Fraunhofer Association at the front of
Institute for economics and also in
Stuttgart
later I've been with IBM as a visiting
scientists and my first subject was
about speech recognition and speech
understandings management of natural
language systems so my the subject of my
PhD was how to use the intonation of
spoken dialogues in order to drive a
dialogue between a system and a user but
this was in the early years in the 90s
so it's some years ago and after that I
started with a human-computer
interaction this was also at Fraunhofer
Society and now since about nine years
I'm as UID
I am responsibility of first for the
software development team and also for a
market branch which we call enterprise
solutions this is a market branch
dealing with enterprise software for
fire for the financial sector for
assurance companies for instance or also
for with software tools
i des or something like that yeah our
audience is relatively relatively
technical so they probably know five
programming languages each and they
probably don't know much about usability
engineering and human-computer
interaction all that you know this this
space of stuff so please give us an
introduction about what usability
engineering is and why this relevant
okay before I start with it I just want
to say a few words about UID so what is
the mission of our company and the name
the full name of UID is user interface
design so you had easy abbreviation and
user interface designs is exactly what
we offer
this is services about how to design how
to model a user interface but also how
to program it and we offer these
services to a very broad range of
applications starting from the
enterprise solutions which I already
mentioned but also to consumer goods
like mobile phone or DVD recorder or
something like that
also ticket sell and automata noir in
the industry sector for welding machines
for instance on the car manufacturing
industry automotive engineering things
like that and the idea of fizzy
foundation of the company was that if a
psychologist and the computer scientist
if they try to work together they should
be able to build more or say better user
interfaces with respect to how they meet
the requirements of the users and this
is basically what is usability is about
is how can we better meet the
requirements that the users have how can
we okay can we develop products that fit
to the goals to the tasks that a user
and have so it's always about the users
that is what usability is about hours
after user about
the tasks asks a user about goals and
also know knows a user profiles know
about their education and things like I
said so so in some sense it's a
counterpoint to the typically typically
engineering technical engineering driven
development process where you might have
advocate the user of the of the system
right it's not functional written or
also the functions should be chosen in a
way that say meets any tasks of and
codes of the user and you already met
talked about your enterprise solutions
path or pop and you talked about
appliances so before we delve into the
details about how usability engineering
applies to software that you maybe want
to talk about the overall scope a little
bit I mean it's actually really broad
you look at how you look at software and
how it interacts I guess so your
question is about a more holistic you
know of holistic product view so it's
not only software inside a product for
instance if you think about embedded
systems take ticket autumn automation
it's not only software inside so in
ticket automatic but it's also in the
hardware and it's all the buttons on the
heart and the display which is use and
so it's the complete product and
usability engineering not only deals
with the usability aspect of the
software but also how the software and
hardware how this is integrated yeah
consider for instance soft keys and so
you can easily think of how the display
must be designs that it's obvious for
the user which labels are related to a
certain F key and etc from your
perspective what is easier you get a
piece of hardware like let's say the
iPhone and you design an application so
that it runs on that hardware given its
you know hardware buttons and stuff or
is it easier if you get a task
and maybe a piece of software to design
the hardware around it is there any
prejudice which one is easier or it's
hard to say which one is easier of
course the interaction designers always
like the most degree of freedom so if we
just have these they say the task to
design a system which should meet some
specific user goals and we are free and
designing also the author and the number
of keys you use and and things that's
always better and it's of course it's
always more joyful interaction and I
guess as leads to this whole topic
whether it's good to have a generic
device that then Randall runs all kinds
of software or whether it's better to
have maybe several specific devices say
it's a heavily this discussed issue
whether you should have dedicated
devices was only a minor number of
functions or whether you have this
unique device which which serves almost
everything so do you really want to
watch TV with your mobile or such and
such a question some people like it and
others just want to make a phone call
and those people still exist yeah I'm
putting myself into the role of a
typical software developer and I know
maybe the development process like like
like the rational process or maybe some
agile stuff how from 10,000 feet
thus the usability engineering fit in
where do I need to talk to usability guy
as soon as possible possible so right in
the beginning you should start ask the
users and get a picture of what your
target group is and and what say I want
to do so this is basically in the
requirements phase or even sooner so
that you really know who I your users
what do they want to do and what is a
background and also you need to know the
environment and we
your product should be used so it's if
it's not just software running on an
ordinary PC or on a laptop or whatever
but think about medical devices or in an
industries construction or welding
machine or Nothing fly like that so you
need to know about the what we call the
context of use and the context the
context of use is a very important it's
very important information for the
interaction designer and context of use
is made of a description of the users
and of their tasks of the environment
and environment not only means the
physical environment but also
organizational environment or if you
think about a workflow if there are any
dependencies between certain steps you
need to know this before you start the
design of a system yeah you already I
it's interesting to see if if you talk
to software developer and you talk about
usability he usually thinks about how to
arrange the widgets in the UI and you
talk about interaction design so it's
already hints at the fact that you see
this way more broadly yeah then what
typically the UI designer things it is
yeah this is a typical mistakes its
software developers often think if you
just have a good say user interface
style guide which tells you how to
position certain widgets on on your
surface that's all but this is what I
would call something like a micro
usability so it's it's more about the
workflow and it's more about the
interaction as a flow of interaction the
navigation and then things like I did
not just arranging things on a screen so
the the way I actually got aware of UI
design was that a customer that I work
with one of my customers had a UI
prototype created by you there the
challenge was to show a lot of
information
on a screen and you were able to focus
on different parts of it and you had to
show overview of the stuff you didn't
focus on and then if you select
something else the other stuff had to
somehow fade out you'll still be shown
in a kind of summary with color codes
and stuff and I was actually really
impressive and that got way beyond what
you do with standard windows controls
for example yeah exactly and this brings
up another topic this is a topic of data
visualization right which is very
important so for instance if you have
huge amounts of data
think about thousands or ten thousands
of data records and if you get a search
result with several thousands hits then
how could you present them to the user
without hitting it just shown as a list
so you might think of other other
approaches of visualize a visualization
but there is a very related topic I come
across all the time I work a lot in
model driven development so I have to
use you and sometimes and if you look at
today's UML tools they're still built in
a way that well the diagrams are
basically passive they look like on a
big sheet of paper that can be printed
there is no interaction of the use of
with the data
I like general diagrams dynamically
opening and you have a poly Aries or
something as it really becomes very
interesting if you can play at it with
data so just see what the future might
bring so a few many pure eight the data
and visualize how a certain result which
change in future if you manipulate the
data this thing was which we deal when
we talk about data visualization and how
to interactively play with the data and
and many tools don't do that they were
still in the CI premiere for it's a pity
okay so um when I prepared the episode
by looking at some of your material
there were a couple of things I wanted
to hit that one is that when designing a
system there are three
mentions user tasks and environment can
you maybe talk about that those those
three and how to interact and also maybe
putting the idea of personas into into
this into this discussion some people
already know about Aaron Cooper one of
the say grandfathers of person of living
persona idea
meanwhile I've just noticed that John
Pruitt released a book about personal
life cycle it's more than 700 pages but
only dealing with the creation of
personas and their life cycle starting
from the childhood so it's a topic of
itself but so but other people might not
know what a person tries so a persona is
stereotypic user but it's derived from
furnaces from interviews or from
material from your marketing department
so if you already have certain model or
certain idea about your target groups
and about the correct characteristics of
your target groups then you try to build
a persona which typically represent one
typical user of a certain target group
and this persona it's not abstract but
it has certain characteristics so you
can somehow immerse into this person so
you get an idea how's this persona might
interact with the system and this
persona can be taken up in your team in
order to discuss how user wizards is
that particular background might
interact with the system and it also
helps to discuss the system design with
your customers so you can take these
personas in order to have people immerse
into a particular user and imagine how
this particular user might interact
with with a system personalizes really
have four means in order to think about
your future users and and just to maybe
emphasize it it's not like the use case
guy you know the stuff that the sticky
the stick the stick figure we can say
bank account user and that's it you
really build I don't know you write
fifty pages about the guy's background
about heavy things so it's it's it's way
further way more yeah and I have a brief
anecdote just from one of our customers
and they really built up personas and
really man-size it physically and so if
the software developers made Fault in
the interaction concept and they just
got one of these personas and put this
persona right behind the neck off the
software developer and yeah they said
watch your persona he is watching you
yeah and just looking over your shoulder
if you do the things right in the way
and the users wanted to have it so so
personas are the way how you represent
users basically in the design process
yes you represent users and you take
some in order to discuss a certain
scenario yeah and I just wanted to take
issue about the use case and scenario
you call it certain scenario or even
narrative scenario so the use case is
like an abstract modeling of the
interaction flow of a system there else
in a scenario we try to describe a
certain episode in the interaction about
the interaction with the system so it's
real or say this persona but with real
tasks and real data so it's not abstract
data but these scenarios help to think
about how the system
will be used in future and how users
will work with a system with a
particular concrete data set and
starting with this narrative scenario we
call it a narrative scenario because
it's like a like an epic story it's a
story it should not be too long just
half a page or things like that or a
page not 20 pages story on because it
would be hard to tomorrow and so if you
have this half page story you can take
that story and build from that a
storyboard and which which shows screen
by screen how the system would behave
since your company does this kind of as
its main focus and full-time of course
we have to expect that you have a
process an engineering process for doing
it it's the UI what is called you I am
engineering it's a user interface
engineering model right right yeah and
so I think to give people somewhat more
thorough understanding of all this stuff
why don't we step through it in some
detail
so so people understand what's what's
going on or what's involved in actually
you know doing UI or interaction design
the right way so I guess the first the
first part is the planning of the
overall system
yeah before we start with you um I just
want to stress as as we our service
provider and we sometimes we only offer
some usability services for to a
customer for instance if a customer it
does also develop by its own or by its
own teams and so I just want to
if I usability test for instance just a
test in order to see whether users can
really work with a system we have just
do the usability test or if you do the
software development of the user
interface also we always have to adapt
to the processes of our customers so how
a user interface engineering model it
helps us to discuss was a customer which
kind of services with regard to use
abilities I want to get from us if they
do not have such or any development
process and you may laugh but this
happens then we we can talk about the
typical phases we got to to product
development and we have speed as a model
up into his basic four phases which you
may know from the rational unified
process or as a HR processes and just to
see in which phase the customer
currently is with his product
development and how we can help them in
order to get a better usability into the
product in other words like in every
reference model it's not intended to
necessarily be done completely in
sequence but it's a way of thinking
about the or exactly exactly yeah okay
so first phase is probably the I think
it's called elicitation and yes the
situation is a rational unified process
that's what we call yeah something
something like the planning phase and
yeah this is also a very critical
starting point that customers often do
not think about usability goals so in
the elicitation phase we wouldn't like
to our customers not only to think about
business goals also usability goal might
also become business goal but also to
think about what they want to achieve as
a new product with regard to usability
and it's not just to be easy to use so
there might be other goals and this is
hard to find out for the customers
because you know certainly the Dilbert
cartoon with many requirements thousands
of requirements and at the end of the
cartoon but it's our mentioning that one
important requirement has been missing
and this is easy to use requirement but
sits that's not just any easy to use but
it's far more for instance you want to
reduce the training effort for complex
system so it's also not only efficiency
because there is there was an ISO norm
which defines usability as the degree of
effectiveness efficiency and
satisfaction was which users can
accomplish tasks but it's not only a
efficiency and effectiveness and even
satisfaction today we talk more about
the joy of use or joy ability and we
think user interfaces should motivate
users in order to to work with an
especially when you think about
commercial products in the consumer
electronics era yeah so usability goes
this one thing with which you you should
start just to think about it and to
initiate the process to think about
usability codes the other thing is of
course its requirements is regard not
only functional requirements but if you
take into account subs model of the
rational unified process functional
requirements and usability safety and
reliability and thinking things like
that then
usability requirements is one set of
the requirements and as a description of
the target user groups so you should
know which target user groups you want
to address and yeah and things like that
so services I just wanted to explain one
thing more it's because we we haven't
caught that usability engineering model
but user interface and engineering model
you might have noticed that and this is
because it's all about the user
interface and this means it's not just
usability but it's also visual designers
graphic design and it's also it's a
technical part of it so we basically we
have three lines and smaller it's one
which regards usability another one
regards the design issues and the next
one regards the software development
process and I want to race one thing
about the design line this is which
emotional aspects should be evoked
wasn't graphical design and so also the
design line starts very early in in
order to find out which requirements a
customer might have with regard to the
visual design how should it look like
and how should the future user interface
look like and also which say which
attractive do you want to associate with
a user interface should it be cool like
right so this is all in the very start
of in the early start of the project to
to know about the design facts about the
design requirements with regard to
visual design but also with regard to
the techno technology which should be
used as a WPF is it Silverlight is it
some something different
and because this also builds the the
sciencebase which we need to take into
account whenever limits it limits yes
exactly so the next phase yeah next
phase would be what usually is called
the modeling phase and here with regard
to the user interface you you have
numerous number of methods which you
could apply but by the way I would like
to explain how the model is constructed
so we we have these phases and for each
face and each line so we have this
realizability design and software
development in each of these lines you
have certain activities per phase so for
instance one activity could be the
requirements analysis in one line and in
order to do a requirements analysis you
have certain methods for instance if you
want to do an interview with with users
and doing an interview is as a method
but as you can use this method not only
during the requirements phase but you
can also use interview for instance in
an evaluation phase this is that methods
are independent from from a face you
just have certain number of medicine's
methods that you might apply in in a
certain phase and for a certain line and
even within a method you might have
tasks which can be which are needed for
different methods for instance if you
want to recruit users for doing such an
interviews or if you want to recruit
gives us for a focus group or you want
to recruit users for doing a usability
test so recruitment would be a task
which could
appear in different methods so this is
how the model is built you have
activities for doing these activities we
have methods and was in a message you
might have tasks okay so with regard to
to modeling if we just take up this
persona issue which we have been talking
about send personas and so with the
creation of personas this one starting
point or could be one starting point
also the creation of narrative scenarios
which then leads to 2 story bots so
these storyboards they show the behavior
of the system screen by a screen but not
in a visual design way but rather in an
abstract way what we call wireframes so
it's basically a sketch or something
yeah you could even do it on paper so
paper prototyping is really cheap and
fast and we try to convince our
customers at its mercy to start on paper
instead of using computer-based tools
but just have some scribbles their paper
and discuss with with your customer do
you know this book the back of the
napkin
it's about visual communication and how
to convince people of your ideas using
visuals yeah and the guy maybe it would
be interesting to read yeah and him this
guy also talks about forget about video
and PowerPoint just take a pen yeah and
there's also a book by Karen Schneider I
called paper prototyping so it's a book
just dealing only with the issue of
paper prototyping and also how to do
usability tests was a prepper prototype
so you do not need to have an
interactive prototype which is program
programmed but you can do usability
tests like an a visit of Awesome Anna
was a paper sorry was a paper portal
there and I guess the the photoshopped
visuals also appear in this face or are
they later you know they appear
this face but just to have one certain
screen designed in order to discuss the
aesthetics of the feature interface we
do not do the storyboard who is right
with Photoshop these designs Photoshop
stuff is really about the visual graphic
design even impression about that right
and then the logical structure of the
screen and the stuff is done the more
simpler means exactly okay mm-hmm
anything else interesting in that phase
yes at the end of the phase we should
have something like a user interface
specification or target or both it
depends sometimes customer already has a
style guide or sometimes we derive a
style guide from the prototypes and in
order to you just describe in patterns
best practices for designing a user
interface for product family like that
but also here I think it's important to
explain the difference between a style
guide and specification but I expected
okay this tag ID again it's a more
abstract it's just this describing for
instance how a certain widget should be
used so what is the purpose of a certain
rigid so if you think about a tree
control what can you do with a tree
control in an abstract way what happens
in the tree control if you click on one
of these small science science and but
it does not put the tree control into
context this is what the user interface
specification does specification
describes the whole system right and the
style guide is basically a collection of
patterns and the software engineering
parents kind of way it says whenever you
use a tree control do it this way so
it's consistent yeah this diet is about
considered yeah consistency across
so it was in a product family yeah but
but I guess that the style that you talk
about here are more domain or
application or product specific than for
example a java swing style guide or a
window style guide it's it's it's it's
tailored to the kinds of stuff the
application yeah yeah often java swing
style guide or Windows is like that with
this target is taking as a basis and and
it's developed further right in order to
cover particular needs of customer yeah
okay next phase is the actual
construction or implementation or the
building of the system often we face a
problem that even if user interface
specification nexus or even if s target
exists then still some say degree of
interpretation freedom is left to the
developers and this is where we support
the development team in order to clarify
issues for instance if the user
interface specification is not a
complete specification of all screens
and as I have to adapt to new workflows
then new questions arise and this is
where the usability engineer might
support the software development team in
in order to derive solutions from former
already specified user interface to
choose a new workflow to extrapolate
from what already there that of course
well implementing the user interface is
basically kind of in that sense it's
trivial so somebody has the program it's
a lot of work of course yeah but it's
not necessarily a lot of work for you
guys yeah what I also want to raise here
is a test topic right so in the
construction phase you have testing and
especially with regard to usability
testing we distinguish between two
different ways of doing usability tests
or
say it's more it's the objective of a
usability test one is more formative a
formative test this is a kind of
usability test which we use in the
modeling phase it is
yeah it's has very much to do with the
idea it's you test in order to change
and but not in order to prove that the
system has met all requirements and you
know if you want to do testing like in
quality assurance ways and this is
courses we call summative tests because
it's a more more least at the end of the
development phase so to have a kind of
few tests with more users various if you
have this formative testing you only
need to have six or eight users or maybe
even four it's important just to have
some users and to see whether they can
work with a system and to take the
results of such a formative test in
order to drive development process and
how do you actually test the UI do you
put users in front of it and measure how
long it takes them to do something and
how happy they are after doing it or I
mean you know how do you do it yeah it's
a mixture of an interview and also using
questionnaires and but the most
important thing is that users try to a
quizzes system was real tasks so you
before you start with a usability test
you have a session and then in the
session as a moderator who leads the
participant through the usability test
and then the participant of such a test
they try to solve tasks and what is
really important is that we ask them to
think aloud to think about what they
expect from the user interface for
instance if they do not find a
particular
option within a menu we ask them about
what they look for so sometimes it's
just the wording issues so that the
wrong labels have been chosen and he's
thinking aloud technique is important to
to get an idea about the users
expectations so they try to solve a task
and then we measure whether they succeed
without help but as I need some help or
was as I cannot succeed even with a lot
of help so it's the number of errors or
the number of help needed with regard to
the completion of a task one issue and
we also use at the end of the test we
often use a questionnaire what we which
is called attractive there's also a
website on it and the attractive
question is used in order to measure the
the attractiveness of a product which is
built up from the pragmatic aspects and
hydronic aspects and the pragmatic
aspects is whether all the functions are
available that a uses that users need NZ
hydronic aspects as well as I like to
work at the visit and this is a
questionnaire which has been validated
and also by by our sensors a website
about the situation but of course you
can also use you can only use it if you
really have visual visually designed
user interface in order to get a writing
yeah and then I guess well okay the last
deployment phase is probably rather
straightforward
yeah the deployment phase might lead
again to the planning phase and you know
so it's an important to get back
feedback from the users and to
like an issue tracking their way yeah
okay so that was basically our stepping
through the UI engineering model a
couple of more questions one is if you
are an agile shop we were doing XP or
something then all of this sounds very
heavy weight and of course you aligned
it with the rational unified process so
it kind of turn agile person has to
sound heavyweight so how do you how do
you integrate that or how do you
convince an agile team XP team or
whatever to to to to put that into their
schedule into their process how would
you how would you make this feel more
agile yeah one important thing is that
even in an aged process process you I
would say you must think about so you
use and not in an abstract way but
really to bring a user into the team for
instance if you consider a scrum
model and you define a sprint and you
might even define as a sprint there's
some activities in which you involve the
users and at the end of the Sprint you
should have results from saying from
usability tests like a spike spike in
usability yeah yeah yeah exactly and but
a problem which is often discussed is
with regard to HR processes and
usability that the question that is
asked is what happens if the user
interface as such changes with each
iteration can we do that or shouldn't we
we do that but I think this depends on
whether really with each iteration you
have market-ready product on or not
so as long as you're not on the market I
would say it's okay to change them user
interface that's to me somehow this
whole discussion about how something
like that fits
to the HR process is a little bit
similar to how do you fit in
requirements engineering and how do you
fit in architecture
you know these somewhat more let's say
strategic aspects of software
development how do you fit those into
the relatively fine granular work
attitude of agile processes and I guess
some of the answer is that you know some
some things aren't useful to do in one
day iterations you sometimes have to do
something a little bit more
strategically what has happened with
regard to HR process is that now we have
something like HR usability engineering
for Francisco temblor has he also has
modeling in angelarc attack okay so it's
every good thing is getting a job first
as I said I I saw some of your work with
with this customer and and to me I mean
it it it really was impressive and it
convinced me personally that at least in
that situation it makes a lot of sense
to have professional usability folks
involved so how do I convince my project
manager or my boss I mean because most
people say well you know it's not
important as long as we can click here
and you know most people I would argue
or many people don't really care at
least initially until they notice there
are problems how do I convince my boss
the first thing is pretty easy it's user
interfaces like calling cart of your
product is the first thing your customer
or user interacts with so if the user
interface is not convincing then people
might refrain from buying such a product
but they say okay then I just I call a
designer and you make some nice and I
can yeah I mean convincing somebody to
get a graphics guy and to have a couple
of nice like a nice colors okay people
get that but to go further and and
really do more than that and think about
efficient interactions and stuff that's
I think for me that's a tougher
challenge to sell to my customers or
consulting clients or something
so it was regard to to the web it's also
rather easy to convince your customers
so if you talk about the conversion rate
if you think about a business if you
think about shops and there have been a
number of studies which show how often
customers do not succeed in buying a
product within a shop today you may know
jack up needs and recognitions alert fox
is a youth and you can find a number of
C's thanks well other any numbers where
people can or where you can that you can
show that you know there's product X
before user interface design involvement
five clicks of our customers and after
it was improved more like numbers to
show that this stuff is actually yes you
can find such numbers in the book first
bias and may its cost justifying
usability as a lot of such numbers but
also in the internet there is the
usability professional association
website you see you pass off but walk
also usability net with an another
website you can find the show notes yeah
yeah but it's also sometimes it's the
customer who wants to prove that the
cost of usability of the usability
measures that it's really pays off yeah
and to give you one example we have
designed call center software
and one usability goal from the customer
worsted to that we should be able to
show as it's a training time the
training effort has really reduced by
means of redesigned user interface yeah
and what we did when we have when we had
finished the user interface design we we
did tests in parallel with the former
system and with a new system and we
started having people so you may
consider summertime and students have in
the call center and if a student just
works for say six weeks yeah well things
like that Casas that doesn't work to
have a training face of colleagues so we
did this test in parallel with the old
system and with a new system having an
initial test in order to see how people
can work with the system without any
training and then after that we had some
more measure points in order to see how
[Music]
effective the and how efficient the
people work with the system and we could
show that we were able to decrease the
learning curve by fifty percent so and
it's really pays off as of here yeah so
is there any material people can look at
except maybe for some of the websites
you already mentioned so if people want
to get involved in the stuff then any
books for example
hint hint of course a number of books a
book of my own it is in German it's use
the court user interface tuning in fact
it's the editor of this book and it's
showing some stories how companies used
usability or how they apply to usability
engineering in
in order to build better usable products
but of course I was numerous number of
English books
so we box by Jakob Nielsen for the web
design in Cooper I've been mentioned
left be before or Jennifer priests you
may know I don't know do you put links
on yeah we will put we'll put those
books on so I know you after the show at
some point we'll put the stuff I will
pass some links yeah reviews okay
okay so um that's basically all is there
anything else you want to say as closing
words to our listeners there's only one
closing words you ask your user sure
okay so thank you very much you're
welcome thank you
[Music]
thanks for downloading and listening to
software engineering radio soft
engineering radio is an educational
program brought to you by hillside
Europe if you want more information
about the podcast and all the other
episodes visit our website at SE - radio
dotnet if you want to support us you can
donate to the SU radio team via the
website or you can advertise press your
radio for example by clicking on the
dick reddit delicious and slash dog
puppies to contact the team please send
email to team at se - radio net or if it
is specific to an episode please use the
comments facility on the website so
other people can react to your comments
this episode of se radio as well as all
other episodes are licensed under
creative commons 2.5 license please see
the website for details thanks to
Charlie Crowell and the Passaic Music
Network for the music used in the show
the song is called Vegas hard rock
shuffle
[Music]